<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Prometheus to APT-Dater</title>
    <link>https://webhippie.github.io/prom-to-apt-dater/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Prometheus to APT-Dater</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://webhippie.github.io/prom-to-apt-dater/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://webhippie.github.io/prom-to-apt-dater/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://webhippie.github.io/prom-to-apt-dater/about/</guid>
      <description>This services can generate automatically hosts configuration files for apt-dater from Prometheus targets which get fetched from the regular API. You can use the builtin filter mechanism powered by Govaluate to limit the hosts and to gather the server group, name and address.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>https://webhippie.github.io/prom-to-apt-dater/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://webhippie.github.io/prom-to-apt-dater/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>Installation So far we are offering two different variants for the installation. You can choose between Docker or pre-built binaries which are stored on our download mirror and GitHub releases. Maybe we will also provide system packages for the major distributions later if we see the need for it.
Docker TBD
Binaries TBD
Configuration We provide overall three different variants of configuration. The variant based on environment variables and commandline flags are split up into global values and command-specific values.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building</title>
      <link>https://webhippie.github.io/prom-to-apt-dater/building/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://webhippie.github.io/prom-to-apt-dater/building/</guid>
      <description>As this project is built with Go you need to install Go first. The installation of Go is out of the scope of this document, please follow the official documentation. After the installation of Go you need to get the sources:
go get -d github.com/webhippie/prom-to-apt-dater cd $GOPATH/src/github.com/webhippie/prom-to-apt-dater All required tool besides Go itself are bundled or getting automatically installed within the GOPATH. We are using Go modules to keep the used tools consistent to manage the dependencies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>License</title>
      <link>https://webhippie.github.io/prom-to-apt-dater/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://webhippie.github.io/prom-to-apt-dater/license/</guid>
      <description>This project is licensed under the Apache 2.0 license. For the license of the used libraries you have to check the respective sources.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>